Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Asta lost the use of his arms after Vero cast an ancient hex on him.
His only hope of lifting the curse lies with the Queen of the Forest of Witches.
But...
The Queen is more deadly than you can imagine.
So much so that the Diamond Kingdom won't even try to stand against her.
And there's no hope of reasoning with her either.
We're going. Whatever it takes for us to heal Asta's arms.
Meanwhile, Vanessa, who hails from said forest, had also returned there in hopes of bargaining for Asta's healing.
Over there!
But when Asta and his friends finally reach the Queen's palace...
Take your foot off of her!
She's one of us! So leave her alone!
Pitiful fools. What could such imperfect creatures possibly hope to do for her?
Okay.
I didn't expect it to happen so soon.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Ahaha, couldn't ask her.
More followers on Mars
ماaaa...
Some hair is completely bigger than me at once
What?
See you next time.
The Midnight Sun?
Why would they come here?
You're not just making up stories to trick us into not attacking you, right?
Imperfect.
What?
If I were so inclined, I could obliterate every last one of you with naught but a snap of my fingers.
Why would I bother deceiving you?
It's her.
From Neon.
The third eye is bad news.
That big hairy guy that messed up my arms was one of them too.
Then it's safe to say she's just as strong as he was.
She might even be stronger.
This is not good!
I'm always getting caught up in these things.
Let them come.
My superior power will vanquish those imperfect fools with perfect grace.
Go.
Tell my children.
A witch who absconded with one of the magic stones is somewhere within those woods as we speak.
And those vicious humans who took Veto's life are in there as well.
That's true.
They must have been alerted to the presence of the magic stone.
They will pay.
I'll destroy everything and secure the magic stone.
Ha ha ha!
Excellent!
I'm sure Master Leaks will be quite pleased with that.
It appears that they're in the center of the forest with the Queen of Witches.
Go on, Mistress.
Burn it all down so there's nowhere left to hide!
Flame Spirit Magic, Salamander's Breath.
Fly away!
We're at the attack!
The forest!
Whoa.
They've got some really powerful flame magic.
Salamander.
A fire spirit.
Despite not having reached its perfect form, it's already quite strong.
Stronger than my scrying predicted.
Is my ability faltering?
Slight imperfections beget larger imperfections.
No.
There's more of them?
Those are...
Right.
We're close to the border of the Diamond Kingdom.
Yeah.
I see.
So.
It's true.
I'd thought this too was not yet to be.
The forest is being breached by one more entity.
The Diamond Kingdom Army.
I don't believe it.
They're on their way too?
Oh, rats.
And just when I had settled into that aromatherapy soak, what's the big emergency summons for anyway?
It's the third eye.
They're preparing to launch an attack on the Forest of Witches.
During the confusion, we're to enter the forest and capture the Queen without being detected.
Why bother with all this sneaking around when we know this isn't an easy win for us either way?
Because orders are orders.
Well, we know that guy's tough.
He's the one we fought back in the dungeon.
He's still alive.
That's so awesome.
That makes you happy?
This is so unfair.
Why does it have to be this way?
I knew coming here was gonna be risky, but we got forced into a major battle again.
Is this just normal for us now?
That boy.
I think it's Mars.
And the one next to him must be Ladros.
So?
Okay.
Let's protect the forest.
I can take down the Eye of the Midnight Sun and the Diamond Army.
That might be tough without arms.
Right?
I forgot!
Wow, Asta.
That's the whole reason we're here.
Did you not get it the first time?
No, I remember now.
There's just so much going on, it slipped my mind.
Fair enough.
Aw, man!
Captain?
Asta, what are you doing here?
Vanessa!
You're awake!
You had us all worried!
Thank goodness.
Don't do that!
A guy can only take so much stress all at once.
Noelle?
Finral?
You're here too?
Oh, and more familiar faces.
One of whom is shirtless.
Uh, yeah.
It's his favorite thing to do.
Will you please stop telling people that?
It's been so long, Vanessa.
Vanessa!
We came to the Forest of Witches to find a way to get the curse lifted from Asta's arms, too.
It's kind of funny that we all wound up in the same place.
That's right.
Don't you worry, Asta.
I'll make a deal with the Queen and your arms will be back to normal in no time.
Not gonna happen!
Huh?
You'd have to trade your freedom for it, right?
Sorry, but that's a big fat no from me!
What?
Do you even hear how selfish you sound?
This is our only option, you idiot!
I don't think so!
You're the one who's being selfish!
Trying to sneak back to your mom's place without telling us!
That's the dumbest idea ever!
And what would you have done in that situation, Rugrat?
I would've told me what's so funny!
Now, now, you two, let's not fight!
Shut up!
You can't say that!
I'm your superior!
Well, I don't need your help.
I've still got one last resort to fall back on.
Whoa, Asta, be careful!
I'm not a doctor, but it kind of seems like he's lost it.
You're right, this can't end well.
Hey, what are you doing?
This is what I'm doing!
That sword.
Wow, it hurts so bad!
Asta!
What'd you do that for?
That curse is already lodged deep inside of your body.
It doesn't matter how strong you are, Asta.
Sometimes there's just no way to escape your fate.
Oh, so what you're saying is
that I'm stuck like this
unless I let my good friend sacrifice herself?
What kind of guy would I have to be
to go along with something like that?
If fate wants to take my arms,
I'll use my legs to kick fate's butt!
Huh?
You say we ended up here because it was our fate?
Yeah, yeah.
Old Mr. Fate.
Man, I hate that guy.
Why would anybody obey him?
I live how I want,
even if it means kicking fate's ass.
Of course.
That's what Captain Yami said.
One more train!
Stop it!
Don't be so stubborn!
Listen, Asta.
Friends don't exist to be sacrificed.
Friends help you overcome a fate
you can't defeat on your own!
That's why I'm here.
I never intended to just throw my life away.
You want to hear my plan?
I was going to trick the queen,
get your anti-magic power back,
and use it to get the hell out of here!
I mean, what?
Oh, really?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Well, she definitely shouldn't have said so now.
Hey, queen of witches!
If you can heal Asta,
stop standing around and do it already!
Did you forget?
Your forest is in danger!
Asta's itching to get out there and save your people!
He may be stupid, but he's strong.
If you fix him, he'll be a huge help.
Besides,
wherever he goes,
we all follow him!
You're outnumbered!
You'll need every bit of extra muscle you can get!
You're the queen,
so make the smart choice.
Let us help you win this!
I do agree the strength of my daughters would prove imperfect against foes like these.
Very well.
I will not only repair the small one's arms.
They'll be more robust than before.
Wow, really?
Awesome?
You mean I'm gonna be as big and buff as Captain Yami?
She said they would be robust.
That doesn't necessarily suggest you'll get bigger.
Ah!
Come on, please!
There really isn't much point in asking me.
I'm impressed, Noelle.
You've sure got a lot of guts.
I know.
I don't think I've ever seen anybody stand up to the queen like you just did.
Well, I am royalty.
Oh, my legs are shaking like crazy!
Rejoice while you can.
But come what may,
both my foolish daughter Vanessa and the power of that brat's anti-magic sword will ultimately belong to me.
Now blood recovery magic.
Curse-breaking blood-filled cuckoos.
My arms!
They feel so light!
This is awesome!
That spell was really advanced.
And quick, too.
I can see why she's the queen.
Oh, yeah!
I am back in the game!
See?
Look what I can do!
Oh, Oster!
Now I don't have to rub my back against walls when it itches?
Oh, and I can pick my nose again!
But what I'm most excited about is getting back to strength training!
Oh, Oster.
Oh, you never change.
This is sweet!
I can't tell if they're more robust or whatever, but they feel like they're bursting with power now!
Get ready!
It's time to go!
Yeah!
Get ready!
It's time to go!
Yeah!
But...
First, we punish you!
Yeah, don't you ever worry us like that again!
Reckless little idiot!
Take that!
Take your dumb road, too!
Hey, wait!
I didn't feel anything!
Is that reinforcement magic?
Nope!
Just all-natural muscle!
I'm glad you're better, Oster.
Yeah!
Thank you guys for helping me, too!
I have fulfilled my promise.
But our pact is imperfect.
Until you use that strength.
Oh, yeah!
You just wait and see!
Thanks for fixing me up, ma'am.
If it's all right with you, let us take care of the Diamond Troops.
Mars and Ladros?
Well, let's just say that I have a bit of a history with those two.
Sure thing, old man.
They're all yours.
Be careful.
Right.
And, uh, get dressed, would you?
Yeah.
Same to you!
Yes, that's right.
Burn!
You can't surrender after just one blast.
That wouldn't be any fun for me at all.
Look over there!
So, I'm guessing these are the enemies you were telling us about earlier.
Who do they think they are?
Are you ready, Akimo?
Yeah, let's protect the forest!
I've never seen a creature like that!
It's no threat to us at all.
Her Majesty's Gollum!
What do these people want?
Oh, Lady of the Third Eye is marvelous!
Mind-boggling power and unparalleled beauty to match!
Oh, how happy I'd be to have Mistress Fauna on my arm one day!
But for now, I suppose I'll just have to settle for the company of these impudent little witches!
Seize them, sir!
Any who appear valuable should be captured alive!
The ones with exceptional magic abilities will make lovely slaves, I'd wager!
Stop! Let's go!
You okay?
No! A man rescued me? Disgusting!
Hey, what's your problem?
Sorry, but we witches believe that women are the mightier sex.
That's why she gave you an attitude.
Try not to take it personally, kiddo.
First, I'll put out this fire!
Good idea. Thanks, Noelle.
And I'll try to get all the witches to safety.
Please do, Fen'ral.
They're really doing some damage here.
But no matter what, this is still my homeland.
And I'm going to fight for it.
Are you ready, Asta?
Born ready!
Well, there they are.
This should be fun.
We've completed all of our preparations for the attack.
Ooh, sounds like somebody's raring to go.
Even so, uh-uh-uh.
Not so fast.
What'd be the point in tangling with a bunch of small fries?
We'll let both sides fight it out for a while,
and then we'll feast on the survivors.
Right.
Is that them?
So many.
Even with the witches' health,
they've still got us outmatched in magic power.
But it all depends on how we fight.
Don't you agree, Master?
True.
The three of us should split up.
What?
Well, we can't.
I promised you I would keep you safe.
I know, sweetheart.
And I'm grateful,
but now's not the time for chivalry.
I'm sure you know that,
given how brilliant you are
when it comes to military strategy.
It's our only chance of winning.
If you say so.
What a wonderful selection of beautiful slave girls!
No!
That scumbag!
He's trying to kidnap those cute girls!
That's a lot of defense mages.
I'm guessing he's the leader.
Hey, Vanessa!
Can you use your threads to fling me over
to where that ugly guy is?
What?
If I did, you'd be too far out for me to pull back.
You want to fight him in midair with no strings attached?
Yeah, I'll be okay.
If that's what you want, then I trust you!
Hey!
What's he doing?
He's launching right toward us!
Take this!
No, take this!
That's him!
It's the same anti-magic boy who defeated Beto!
Strike him down!
He's using them to climb up!
Wow, who does that?
Well, it is Asta after all.
I've had enough of you guys making a mess of everything!
You stay away from me, boy!
Asta's stronger now.
He's unstoppable!
Just cut it!
No!
This is your chance!
You can't tell us what to do, you man!
And don't expect us to thank you either!
Hurry, let's go!
At last, it's you.
You're the boy who kills Beto!
Uh-oh, I'm dead!
Wait, no!
This will be easy!
Just in time!
Fin roll!
Nice!
You've been getting in our way at every turn.
I'll make sure this is the last time.
Keep on showing up, and I'll just keep on fighting you off.
Good night!
I'll see you next time.
Uh-uh. Not so fast. You can't eat them yet.
The packet says you're supposed to wait three minutes after you add the magic.
But I want to eat them now.
Nope, not so fast.
I like my noodles more firm.
Sorry, but you can't.
Can.
It's too soon.
That's my choice.
Too early.
Hey!
Ready!
Time to eat!
Ah, perfect.
Early!
I'm so glad Asta's arms are better.
And isn't the queen of witches great?
I mean, sure, she's evil or whatever, but if you look at her, she's pretty cute.
Black Clover, page 59.
Flames of hatred.
My magic is appreciating a wide range of lovely ladies.